https://www.havenacs.org/donor-privacy-policy

The Haven ACS' Donor Privacy Policy
This policy applies to all donor information received by The Haven ACS, both online and offline, as well as any electronic, written, or oral communications.
Donor Information We Collect, Store and Use
The Haven ACS collects nonpublic personal information included on forms, checks and gift letters we receive from you, or through information you communicate directly to us through other means. The Haven ACS will only collect information we believe is reasonably useful in administering our business or to provide services to donors.
To the extent any donations are processed through a third-party service provider, our donors’ information will only be used for purposes necessary to process the donation.
Donor Privacy
The Haven ACS will not share, trade, or sell a donor’s personal information; nor do we send donor mailings on behalf of other unaffiliated organizations. Donor information is not disclosed unless to comply with federal or state laws and regulations, or with court orders.
Employee Access to Donor Information and Enforcement
Only employees with a need to know will have access to donor information, and this circle is kept limited. All are trained on our Donor Privacy Policy. Any employee who violates the Donor Privacy Policy will be subject to disciplinary measures (warnings, reprimands, suspensions) and possible termination of employment. Any person with access to our donor records must sign and abide by a confidentiality agreement.
Maintenance of Accurate Information
The Haven ACS will correct known inaccurate information in a timely manner.
Inquiries about donor information and privacy should be addressed to:
